I am Yoshika Akimoto of Team Sachi.
This is Ayaka Kimura of Team Sean.
This is a continuation of our conversation from yesterday.
I look forward to working with you.
We had a lot of fun yesterday,
Let's have fun again today.
Please enjoy today as well.
As has become a regular feature of this nightly dialogue series, we have a question from an idol to an idol,
We have been thinking of questions that we would like to ask each other.
We have thought of some questions we would like to ask each other,
I would like to ask them right away.
May I start?
I'm scared.
Don't be scared.
Can I ask a really normal question?
Please go ahead.
In your mind, you are a vocalist, or rather, you sing a lot, don't you?
When you sing,
I think it's really basic to be conscious when singing.
It's difficult.
I'm not conscious of anything.
But, I wonder.
My voice often sounds really backwards.
Really?
It's easy for me to sound embarrassed.
Is that part of your taste?
But, since the great Aika turns her voice inside out so easily, it's a matter of physical strength.
It comes down to physical strength.
I don't know if I have any stamina at all in my throat, I've been working on it a lot, but I still don't have it.
What do you mean by working out?
I sing in a way that tires my throat easily,
That's why my throat gets tired,
So, I get throat fatigue and end up like, "Oh, my God!
So I tell him to sing from the stomach, and he asks me to do so,
But I don't have the strength in my throat,
I don't want to make an embarrassing sound.
It doesn't lead to any music or anything.
No, but it's great. You've been singing for a long time,
You love singing, right?
I love singing.
When did that start?
I started singing when I was 4 years old,
Since you were 4 years old?
That's right.
Wow.
My mom used to sing, too, so I've always been inundated with singing,
I told her I would let her in.
And then I woke up.
That's right. Singing all the time.
So, from then on, you wanted to be a singer someday.
I always wanted to be a singer.
So you did.
It's already been 7 years since Shin-On,
I didn't think I had a future in Shin-On,
I didn't know what was going to happen in my life.
Look at him from the morning when he was 4 years old.
The morning when I was 4 years old.
That's right.
When did you start singing?How long have you been singing?
I've been singing since I was team president of the Full Body Group.
Since?
I had never been to karaoke or anything like that,
And that's it?
That's amazing!
It's not that I'm a good singer or anything,
It's not that I'm not a good singer, it's just that I enjoy doing it.
That's why,
I see.
I know.
I used to be in a bad way.
Was it bad?
I thought you had been singing for a long time.
None of the members were,
I see.
My friend and the team president also asked me to be an idol for one day only,
We were all in Star Night Stage,
They live in Aichi Prefecture or gathered together,
They asked me to play the role of an idol for one day only.
And that was the beginning.
That's right. That's how it all started,
You've noticed.
It's been 12 years.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Amazing.
It's too amazing.
12 years is my whole life when I join a branch office.
Wait!
That's amazing.
He said that if you recruit for a branch office.
Twelve years is really amazing, isn't it?
That's for sure. I didn't think it would go on like this.
It's amazing.
It's easy.
Enjoying it is the best, isn't it?
Enjoying it is the best, right?
So, what about me?
I have a lot of questions,
That's okay. Ask a lot of questions.
First of all, how often do you go back to Nagoya?
I mean, how long have you been back in Nagoya?
So you're leaving already?
I am. But I'm going back to Nagoya today after this recording.
By bullet train?
Shinkansen.
Do you come here every time you have a concert?
Basically, yes. But they schedule me to continue working in Tokyo, so we all come to Tokyo together to do it,
It's tough.
But, it's a great relief to have a home? Having a home base is a great comfort.
What is the best Nagoya food?
I sound like an old lady.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I was just in Nagoya the other day.
Did you eat?
I didn't eat much,
I had some chicken wings.
But I didn't eat anything at all, like hitsu-mabushi and pasta with starchy sauce,
But I asked people in Nagoya. What's good there? I asked them,
But they told me that people in Nagoya don't eat that kind of food after all.
I do eat them.I'll eat.
You'll eat?
I'm going to eat. I eat.
Only for tourists, because people who live here don't care about that. They said something like that.
They eat a lot,
Because basically, if you order noodles,
If I had a choice, I would definitely order the eraser noodles,
I see. You are a tourist, aren't you?
That's how often I eat.
That's how I was raised, so it has to be that way.
When I go to a ramen shop,
If it's a ramen shop, it's called Sugakiya Ramen,
Yes, I ate it.
You ate it?
It was a cup ramen.
It was delicious.
Yes, yes. That's the taste of Sugakiya.
Not pork bone, not soy sauce, but Sugakiya's taste.
It was really delicious.
I'm so happy.
Do you have any stores?
There are a lot of stores.
I love ramen.
Really?
I had ramen yesterday.
You're eating ramen.
That's why I'm in trouble.
It's a little tight.
But you're still thin today, so you'll be fine.
I can be this thin.
But I'll be back soon for the Nagoya tour.
What would you like?
What do you recommend?
I'd like to buy you a souvenir of the latest fad,
Do you know what a peorin is?
I don't know. Piolin?
It's called a peoline.
What's that?
There's a pudding.
It's a pudding in the shape of a chick sold at Nagoya station,
That's why it's called "Piolin"?
That's right.
What is it?
It's more like a pudding or a bavarois,
Is it pudding?
It's a pudding? - It's a pudding?
But it's too unstable to take home.
This, this, this.
How cute!
It's sold at Nagoya station,
But it's only sold at Nagoya station.
Only in Nagoya?
Yes. It's made with eggs from Nagoya Cochin.
Amazing.
It's so delicious,
But it's unstable when you bring it home,
I want to talk about the process of getting them home safely,
It's called the "Piolin Challenge.
That's so cute!
Yes, it is. So, everyone takes it home and posts on social media that the Piolin Challenge was a success,Yes, that's right. That's why people take them home and post on social networking sites that the Piolin Challenge was a success,
I want you to try it.
If you do that, your face will look like this.
My face looks a little like this.
I don't want to do it. I want to try it.
I often receive them as gifts,
I'm mixed in with such a packy.
It's hard. You want to give it a try? I'll tell the members.
Try it, it's delicious.
I can tell them that Ho-chan said so. I'm glad.
By all means.
I've been selling Piolin's for a long time,
Recently?
Recently, the Piolin Challenge has become even more popular,
There was a huge line.
Is that so?
Face.
Try it. It's delicious.
I'll go buy some.
You'll be pleased.
Thank you.
I'm glad. We had a lot to talk about. We did it.
I was able to play the violins.
Thank you very much.
Now, here is an announcement from Nighttime Toa Idol.
The third event of the Nighttime Toa Idol presents is,
will be held on September 6 at Tokyo Kinema Club.
The title is Tokyo Yakan Land Vol. 3: Roses of Uguisudani.
Fashionable name.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I've heard that many people have been doing this before,
This time, the performers were,
Yuzuki Daikoku from Sachi,
Riju Murahoshi from Ukka,
Battenshojo-tai,
Sepasakura,
Ikinari Tohoku-san, Yosumori Waka
Yosumori Waka,
Fujitani Mew,
Mita Ibuki from Crown Pop,
And Nairuna,
Harimakana,
Kurumi Hori,
Haruna Mai,
and Yaika Kimura from Shin-On,
Aikaman from Shinon,
And more,
A former male actor of Tanazuka,
and now an idol and YouTuber,
and now an idol and YouTuber, Maya Ayaha, is going to appear in the show,
What?
She's going to be in it! Hey!
That's right.
What should I do? What should I do?
In the midst of all this Stardust,
I was chosen,
Oh, my God!
What should I do?
Don't worry.
Yuzuki is from our group, too,
Size.Size.
But you know what, Yuzuki?
I love younger girls.
So you don't mind if I say it like this?
Won't they get mad at you?
I love it when people depend on me,
So, if something happens,
Yuzuki,
What? Just like my mom.
But she seems kind, doesn't she?
She seems patient.
Sometimes, she comes off as a bit of a clunker,
But you have to love me for that, too,
I love you.
Yuzuki is probably the oldest of the group,
Yuzuki is probably the oldest person in the group,
If you need anything, you can go to Yuzuki,
Has anyone else performed with you before?
Have you ever performed with Clownpop?
I had a 3-man show with Clownpop once,
We became great friends at that time,
So, you've played with eveve.
But I haven't really talked with them. With all of you.
That's right. It's not easy to talk with them,
Even if we do, we don't talk with each other properly.
And I get very angry. I am.
Oh, really?
Even though you are so noisy,
I can't say anything when I'm in front of them,
So, one-on-one, you can talk to him, right?
Yes, I think so. Once I'm okay with it, I'm like this.
Is that so?
That's right.
So, tear it up.
Tear it. Tear it right away.
Everyone is very kind, isn't he?
They are very nice. They're all good kids.
You don't have to worry.
They are very helpful.
You can rest assured. That's what I mean.
Do you often go to outside events alone?
No, I don't. I don't have any solo events,
I've never been invited to perform solo,
That's exactly what happened this time,
It's just me.
I'm going to be a part of Starlust, right?
I'm nervous.
I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
That was a great relief. Now.
I want to go see it.
Oh, man. I have to sing properly.
So this means singing and acting?
Yes, that's right. That's what he said.
I don't know what to do. I wonder if I can handle it.
It means I will become someone else, right?
I'll have to abandon my character.
What should I do?
It's going to be okay.
I can do anything.I can do anything.
I can do anything.
Ho-chan will be there for you. It's okay.
Don't worry.
So, for more information about Tokyo YakanLand Vol. 3,
Please check out the official Twitter feed of Kettle and Idol for more information about Tokyo YakanLand Vol. 3.
How was it?
Did you have a lot of fun talking with us?
It was a lot of fun. I had a lot of fun talking with Hou-chan,
I didn't think I had a chance to talk with Hou-chan and her,
I never thought I would have a chance to talk with you alone,
I think you are probably looking at this screen right now,
I hope that your dreams will expand again,
I thought today that I will continue to do my best.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much.
I also enjoyed talking with you,
You talk a lot,
I'm having a lot of fun.
He's even louder.
I want to get to know you better.
Yay!
Volume.
So, I really want to do a 2-man or something.
What?
I want to.
I want to. I want to,
And since Team Shachi is there, too, with Blastai and others,
I would like to work with them someday.
There are some overlaps there as well,
Wouldn't you like to work together?
There are songs that specialize in brass.
We also have songs that specialize in brass,
We have brass-specific songs, and we would like to exchange songs,
I like that one. Edo joshi.
Edo jyojo?
Edo Onna" is written "Edo Woman".
I'm going to be exposed as an idiot.
Don't worry, people don't usually read it that way.
Edo Onna.
I like Edojyo very much.
Everyone said they liked her.
Kawatani-none wrote this song for me,
I'm really happy about that,
Everyone said we should do karaoke someday.
We will do our best to make it happen someday.
A lot,
If everyone's voices are loud enough, we might be able to make this happen,
I would be very happy if you could write your thoughts and comments about today's event.
Thank you very much.
So far, I have been with Honoka Akimoto of Team Orca,
and Aika Sousuke's memorial aika.
Thank you very much.